Alisha: Who’s that?
Tanya: That’s my sister, Lena.
Alisha: How old is she?
Tanya: She’s 30, look at the cake!
Alisha: Oh yeah! Nice cake!
Does she also live in the UK?
Tanya: Yes, she does.
She lives in London too, quite near me.
It’s great, because the rest of my family are all in Germany.
Alisha: What does she do?
Tanya: She’s a journalist.
Alisha: Oh right.
Is she married?
Tanya: She has a partner, Sam.
He’s English.
He works for an IT company.
And this is my brother Stefan with my nephew, Leon.
Alisha: Ahh! How old is he?
Tanya: Leon?
About one.
They live in Berlin –
I don’t see them very often, unfortunately.
Stefan is a great dad!
Alisha: So what does he do?
Tanya: He’s a chef.
Alisha: Is that another sister?
Tanya: No, that’s my cousin, Nadya, and her husband Alex.
Alisha: She looks very like Lena!
Tanya: Yes, maybe in that photo!
Alisha: So what does Nadya do?
Tanya: She’s a teacher.
And Alex is a police officer.
Alisha: They look very young! How old are they?
Tanya: She’s 24, and he’s 26, I think.
They live in Frankfurt.
We’re very good friends.
Alisha: Nice pics!
Tanya: Thanks.
Can I see some photos of your family?
Alisha: Yeah, sure.
So this is my…
Sorry, Tanya, I need to go.
I have a meeting at half past one.
Tanya: OK.
Alisha: Bye.
Tanya: See you later.